yellow.place 2017-06-18

# Privacy policy

## Dear Website Visitors,

Yellow.Place collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Yellow.Place’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Yellow.Place’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Yellow.Place may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Yellow.Place also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Yellow.Place does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Yellow.Place’s websites choose to interact with Yellow.Place in ways that require Yellow.Place to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Yellow.Place gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with Yellow.Place by purchasing a service are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Yellow.Place collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Yellow.Place. Yellow.Place does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Yellow.Place may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. Yellow.Place may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Yellow.Place does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Yellow.Place discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Yellow.Place’s behalf or to provide services available at Yellow.Place’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using Yellow.Place’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Yellow.Place will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Yellow.Place discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Yellow.Place believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Yellow.Place, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Yellow.Place website and have supplied your email address, Yellow.Place may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Yellow.Place and our products. Yellow.Place takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Yellow.Place uses cookies to help Yellow.Place identify and track visitors, their usage of Yellow.Place website, and their website access preferences. Yellow.Place visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Yellow.Place’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Yellow.Place’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Yellow.Place may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Yellow.Place’s sole discretion. Yellow.Place encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
